In this lesson, you've worked on and created a variety of ways to meet
在本课程中 您已处理并创建了各种方法来满足
business objectives and have seen how they
业务目标 并已看到业务目标
relate to the work you do in creating available,
与您在创建时所做的工作相关
reliable and resilient systems.
可靠的弹性系统
You've measured uptime and downtime and
您已测量正常运行时间和停机时间 并且
seen the intricacies of measuring and reporting on them.
对他们的测量和报告的复杂性
These concepts are not quite simple opposites but need to be
这些概念不是很简单的对立面 而是需要
considered with scheduled maintenance integrated service as well.
也考虑使用定期维护集成服务
We've also calculated RTO and RPO matrix
我们还计算了 RTO 和 RPO 矩阵
to gain an understanding of what they are and how they apply to your business.
以了解他们的情况以及他们对您的业务的应用情况
Disaster recovery is the last line of defense when
灾难恢复是最后一道防线
a major disruption takes place in your main datacenter or region.
主要的中断发生在您的主要数据中心或区域中
You've practiced several options for disaster recovery configurations and
您已为灾难恢复配置和
also identified which AWS services are best suited for your DR needs.
还可以确定哪些 AWS 服务最适合您的 DR 需求
So far we've looked at
到目前为止
the foundational pieces that AWS has in regions and availability zones.
AWS 在区域和可用性区域中的基本部分
The resilience options within applications services and now
应用程序中的弹性选项服务和现在
business objectives and how they tie into availability, reliability, and resiliency.
业务目标及其与可用性 可靠性和弹性的关系
Coming up, we'll discuss monitoring for and reacting to failures within our systems.
接下来 我们将讨论监控系统中的故障并对故障作出反应